<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>projects on Hugo Sibony</title>
    <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in projects on Hugo Sibony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hugosibony.com/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory Home Lab</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/active_directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/active_directory/</guid>
      <description> Active Directory Homelab  Active Directory Administration:  PowerShell: Automated provision, maintaining, and deprovisioning user accounts   Setting up Remote Access Server (RAS) features to support NAT/PAT Implementation and maintenance of Windows DNS and DHCP services Configuration of Windows File Servers with implementation of quotas and NTFS permissions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alias Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/alias_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/alias_manager/</guid>
      <description>Alias Manager Alias Manager is a simple command-line tool written in C for managing aliases in your shell. It supports adding, listing and removing aliases in your shell
Features  Add new aliases with custom commands List existing aliases Remove aliases by name  Installation  Clone this repository to your local machine:  git clone https://github.com/kazetachinuu/alias_manager.git cd alias_manager Install the Alias Manager binary by running the install script:  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BrainFuck Interpreter</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/brainfuck-interpreter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/brainfuck-interpreter/</guid>
      <description>Brainfuck Interpreter This is a simple Brainfuck interpreter written in C.
Table of Contents  Introduction Usage Building  Introduction Brainfuck is an esoteric programming language created in 1993 by Urban Müller. It is known for its extreme minimalism, with the language using only eight simple commands, an instruction pointer, and an array of memory cells, each initialized to zero.
This project provides a basic Brainfuck interpreter that can execute Brainfuck programs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
