<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baichuan Li</title>
    <link>https://www.patrickli.one/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Baichuan Li</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 19:49:32 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.patrickli.one/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to properly mount Google Drive with RClone</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/memos/rclone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 19:49:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/memos/rclone/</guid>
      <description>Install RClone Before we start, you need to install RClone on your computer.
For arch, run
sudo pacman -S rclone Set up Google Drive Remote We need to link RClone with your Google account. Run the following command to start the configuration:
rclone config Press n to create a new remote.
Enter name for new remote. name&amp;gt; TEST Option Storage. Type of storage to configure. Choose a number from below, or type in your own value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 494 Project 3: Cavelit</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/eecs494/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:53:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/eecs494/project3/</guid>
      <description>Hosico Game Studio Presented Trailer What makes Cavelit Exciting? Your mission is to get out of the cave at the end. But remember, it is a real cave! It is dark, humid and dangerous. You might encounter various unexpected dangers such as lava, collapses and spikes. YOUR BATTERY IS DYING! Hurry up and get out.
PLAY IT! Click here if the game does not load </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Control And Isolation</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/eecs388notes/accesscontrolandisolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:13:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/eecs388notes/accesscontrolandisolation/</guid>
      <description>Access Control We aim for: Principle of Least Privilege.
Limit the damage of an accident Reduce interaction to the minimum operator Minimized the number of the program audited. ( e.g: My office key can only open my office door. )
( e.g: Classified information of &amp;ldquo;need-to-know&amp;rdquo; )
Models and Policies Security Model
Subject (Who); Apps, Users, Web Origins Objects (What): Files, Processes, Devices, DB Tables, Cookies Operations: Read, Write, Call This security model defines an Access Control Matrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Hijacking</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/eecs388notes/controlhijacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:09:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/eecs388notes/controlhijacking/</guid>
      <description>Basic Knowledge Registers General Purpose Registers EAX: Used to store return values EBX ECX EDX ESI Special Purpose Registers EIP: Instruction Pointer ESP: Stack Pointer, indicate the top of the function EBP: Frame / Base Pointer, indicate the bottom of the function CPU Instructions (Intel Syntax) Move a value to a register: mov eax, 0x34 Add a value to a register: add eax 10 Jump to a line of code: jmp 0x123 Call a function (returns to the next line): call 0x1234 Stack push 0x0a push 0x6c push 0xff pop eax pop eax push 0x88 overwrite the original value Note that the pop does not eliminate the value of the stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KubeCon Day2</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/kubecon2022/day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:09:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/kubecon2022/day2/</guid>
      <description>This is my second day of the KubeCon Event. I love KubeCon. The opening keynote of KubeCon | CloudNativeCon
KubeCon supports Ukrain
Definitely Something I will need: Kubernetes tutorial
Border between US and Canada
Best activity today: Solution Showcase. A varierty of product from dozens of companies
This is a lovely microK8s cluster built with 4 Raspberry Pi and a switch
The impact of Prometheus. We should use Prometheus to get data in order to utilize our resources as much as possible</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KubeCon Day 1</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/kubecon2022/day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/kubecon2022/day1/</guid>
      <description>This is the first time I have ever paid a visit to a formal academic conference
My Badge of KubeCon
Conference about In-Time data analysis
A nice fuzz generator that can generate random test cases to make your program robust
A high schooler sharing his ideas about open-source development
Gavin said that it reminded him of his high school age.
An online encyclopedia for Cloud Native terminology
I think I will try it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Integrity</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/eecs388notes/integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:15:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/blog/eecs388notes/integrity/</guid>
      <description>Threat Model Alice computes v=f(m), where v is a verifier of the message m. Alice sends the message to Bob via Mallory. Bob verifies that v&#39;=f(m&#39;). Random Function (RF) Set up a random map f: {Fixed size input}-&amp;gt;{Fixed size output}. This function is only known by Alice and Bob, but unknown to Mallory.
Provably secure: Mallory cannot find out the verifier of a message that he has never seen (he cannot do it better than guessing).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SilverFOCS-web</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/vg100/silverfocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:56:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/vg100/silverfocs/</guid>
      <description>Project Description The project was created at the request of Professor Manuel Charlemagne of Shanghai Jiaotong University. We expect the website to demonstrate the masterpieces created by our students in a web game development course. The website is designed to automatically fetch, deploy and demonstrate the student projects. I am currently in charge of leading the general development process.
The website is currently hosted at: https://focs.ji.sjtu.edu.cn/silverfocs/. The accessibility from the US depends on the network status of Shanghai Jiaotong University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 494 Porject 1: Legend of Adlez</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/eecs494/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/eecs494/project1/</guid>
      <description>This is a remake of the first version of Legend of Zelda released by Nintendo in 1986 on NES. This remake includes a revision of the original Dungeon level and most of the core mechanics shipped with the game.
We also added a few new features to the game. I want to keep it a secret here. You can play and explore it all by yourself.
Press X to use your sword and Z to use your alternative weapon (exactly what it was in the original NES game).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EECS 494 Project 2: Swapper</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/eecs494/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/eecs494/project2/</guid>
      <description>How to play How to play this 2-player platform puzzle game? Use WASD for one player and arrow keys for the other. (Sorry I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough time to implement game controller support)
What&amp;rsquo;s new The most interesting part of a platform puzzle game is that the 2 players should cooperate as much as possible! They should think hard together to find a path. In this game, I introduced a new way to cooperate: the players can switch their colors and therefore, their abilities to pass the levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaseci Project</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/clarity/jaseci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:32:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/clarity/jaseci/</guid>
      <description>The Jaseci Mission The mission of Jaseci is to accelerate and democratize the development and deployments of end-to-end scalable AI applications. To this end, Jaseci presents a novel set of higher level abstractions for programming sophisticated software in a micro-service/serverless AI and a full stack architecture and programming model that abstracts away and automates much of the complexity of building applications on a distributed compute substrate of potentially thousands of compute nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SilverFOCS Calypso</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/vg100/silverfocs-calypso/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.patrickli.one/portfolio/vg100/silverfocs-calypso/</guid>
      <description>What is this Calypso is a game that we submitted as our project for the game development and management course called VG100 at Shanghai Jiaotong University. It is an exploration game where the player can walk around and interact with NPCs. The entire game is a single-page web application written in Elm.
Technical ELM: A newly-introduced functional programming language Git: Basic skills to manipulate git repositories Project Management: When starting a project, coding comes last: Otherwise, we may waste our efforts on useless development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
