<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Hugo Sibony</title>
    <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Hugo Sibony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 17:41:36 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory Home Lab</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/active_directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/active_directory/</guid>
      <description>Active Directory Homelab  Active Directory Administration:  PowerShell: Automated provision, maintaining, and deprovisioning user accounts   Setting up Remote Access Server (RAS) features to support NAT/PAT Implementation and maintenance of Windows DNS and DHCP services Configuration of Windows File Servers with implementation of quotas and NTFS permissions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alias Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/alias_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/alias_manager/</guid>
      <description>Alias Manager Alias Manager is a simple command-line tool written in C for managing aliases in your shell. It supports adding, listing and removing aliases in your shell
Features  Add new aliases with custom commands List existing aliases Remove aliases by name  Installation  Clone this repository to your local machine:  git clone https://github.com/kazetachinuu/alias_manager.git cd alias_manager Install the Alias Manager binary by running the install script:  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BrainFuck Interpreter</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/brainfuck-interpreter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/brainfuck-interpreter/</guid>
      <description>Brainfuck Interpreter This is a simple Brainfuck interpreter written in C.
Table of Contents  Introduction Usage Building  Introduction Brainfuck is an esoteric programming language created in 1993 by Urban Müller. It is known for its extreme minimalism, with the language using only eight simple commands, an instruction pointer, and an array of memory cells, each initialized to zero.
This project provides a basic Brainfuck interpreter that can execute Brainfuck programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track by TrueFalse</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/trackbyprometech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/trackbyprometech/</guid>
      <description>Track Track is a cloud-based scraping tool that allows you to scrape data from any website and send it to your Discord server.
Click on the logo to go to the project&amp;rsquo;s website.

How does it work? Track uses Discord Webhooks to send the data to Prometech&amp;rsquo;s servers, which then sends it to your Discord server.
How do I use it? You can send a project request on Prometech website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainfall Analyser</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/rainfallanalyser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/rainfallanalyser/</guid>
      <description>Rainfall Analyser / Visualizer This is a coursework for my Java course at JCU.
I have to implement a rainfall analyser that can read data from a csv file and output the result to another file.
I also implemented a visualizer that can visualize the rainfall data in a bar chart.
We had to build a GUI for this project using JavaFX.
Features  Read data from a csv file Visualize the rainfall data in a bar chart  The GUI allows the user to select a csv file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCR Sudoku Solver</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/ocr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/ocr/</guid>
      <description>OneToNine First defence for OCR Project at EPITA by four A2 students.
How to use Solve a Sudoku Board cd Solver/ make ./solver &amp;lt;boardFilename&amp;gt; It will write the solution in the file &amp;lt;boardFilename&amp;gt;.result.
The XOR Perceptron cd Neural_Network/ make ./perceptron &amp;lt;nbEpochs&amp;gt; (or by default 10_000) It will train the XOR perceptron and display the result of the training each 100 epochs and save the result in xor.nn.
Image Processing cd IMGProcess/ make .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowpack Proxy Server</title>
      <link>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/snowpack-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hugosibony.com/portfolio/project/snowpack-proxy/</guid>
      <description>Snowpack Proxy Server Snowpack Proxy Server is a simple proxy server implementation using Boost.Asio.
Table of Contents  Introduction Features Getting Started Usage Commands  Introduction Snowpack Proxy Server is a lightweight proxy server built with Boost.Asio, designed to facilitate communication between multiple users. It allows users to connect and exchange messages through a central proxy, providing a basic foundation for distributed systems and communication testing.
Features  Basic proxy server functionality Asynchronous communication using Boost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
